Diana Davies Papers, 1960s-1996 (ongoing)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
Diana Davies papers
1960s-1996 (ongoing)
Davies, Diana, 1938-
MS 309
57 boxes (17 linear ft.)
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
Musician; Photographer; Artist; Theater worker. Papers consist primarily of Davies' photographs of individuals and groups, musicians, artists, political activists in the civil rights, peace, anti-poverty, and feminist events (marches, demonstrations, conferences, etc.); celebrities, musicians, politicians, and street people. Included is material related to her publication Photojourney: Photographs; fliers, broadsides; memorabilia; and artwork.
Musician, theatre worker, and photographer Diana Davies became a photojournalist in the 1960s. One of the principal documentarians of the second-wave women's movement the U.S., she also photographed in Africa, Central America, the Middle East, and Europe. She documented the civil rights and peace movements, poor people's and welfare rights movements, and farmworkers' struggles. Throughout her career, Davies has photographed various creators and performers of cultural expression, including musicians, writers, craftspersons, dancers, circus and theatre people, potters, and artists. Her photographs of individuals run the gamut, from obscure street people to well-known public figures. Davies' work has been published in books, journals, newspapers, and magazines, and is included in collections at the New York Public Library, the Smithsonian Institution, Howard University, and the Swarthmore Peace Collection. Her book Photojourney: photographs was published in 1989.
In the 1990s, Davies abandoned her career in photography (except for photographs of friends) in order to work as a graphic artist, painter and illustrator, with an emphasis on the subject of social change. Davies writes plays with social justice themes, having throughout her life participated in and supported all aspects of "people's theatre." As a committed peace and social justice activist she also works with organizations promoting social change, and helps feed and clothe the needy in her community.
The Diana Davies Papers consist primarily of her photographs of individuals and groups, musicians, artists, political activists in the civil rights, peace and feminist movements; celebrities and politicians; women's events (marches, demonstrations, conferences, etc.); and images of a variety of people and events from Broadway actors to New York City street people. As a photojournalist at the height of the Women's Liberation movement, Davies documented many of the important players and events in the movement in New York City in the 1960s and 1970s. The photographs are also a rich source of images of women musicians and "Women's Music." Also included is material related to her publication Photojourney: photographs (1989); exhibit materials; fliers, broadsides, and other printed matter; memorabilia; an audio recording of "Twelve O'Clock Girl in a Nine O'Clock Town," by Davies; and an oral history.
Oversized prints are filed in a separate box at the end of the series. Acid-free photocopies of the oversize photographs are filed in the applicable folder in boxes 1 and 2. In cases where contact sheets contain photographs of more than one subject, acid-free photocopies of the contact sheet are filed in all applicable folders.
Negatives include negatives of the prints above, as well as some negatives for which the SSC does not own prints. Negatives are filed in numerical order. In cases where the Sophia Smith Collection owns the negative for a photograph, the corresponding negative number is written on the reverse side of the print.
This collection is organized as follows:
Biographical material
Published Material
Sistervision exhibit, March 2000
"Diana's Place"
Women's Movement - Women's Lives
PhotoJourney
Poverty-Poor Folk
Northampton State Hospital Squat (1996) and Squatters-Housing Rights movement
Welfare Rights and Economic Human Rights Struggle
"Poor People's Campaign" (a.k.a. Poor People's March), 1968
Civil Rights Movement, 1960s (and African-American History)
People's Struggles: The State of Society and the World
Common Stock - a worker's collective
Labor History
Prison Issues and Prisoner's Rights
Theatre and Public Art
Dance
Street Artists, Musicians, Buskers and Craftspeople
Women and Music: The Soundwomen
Women's Music
Artists, Craftspeople, Architects, Sculptors, Photographers, Video people, Filmmakers, Actors (film)
Writers
The Railroads, Hoboes and Subways
Western Mass. Women; Western Mass Community Groups
Women's Zines and Publications
Street Kids Project, Maine
Mexico, Cuba, Portugal, Spain (and related U.S. scenes)
Israel - Palestine (and related material from New York City)
Animals - Creatures (and more best friends)
Nature and Farms and Coastal Maine (1960s-90s)
The Miscellany Box
Artwork and Design
Videotapes
Additional Material
Oversize prints
Oversize published material and posters
Oversize and odd objects: Found and created goods
Negatives
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The papers are open to research according to the regulations of the Sophia Smith Collection.
This collection has not been fully processed and therefore may be difficult to use.
Additions to the Collection
Periodic additions to collection are expected and may not be reflected in this record.
History of the Collection
Diana Davies began donating her papers to the Sophia Smith Collection in 1997.
Search Terms
Feminists--United States--Photographs; New York (N.Y.)--Photographs; Northampton (Mass.)--History--Sources; Women musicians--Photographs; Women's music--Photographs; Women's rights--New York (State)--New York--Photographs; Lesbians--United States--History--20th century--Photographs; Women photographers--United States--Biography--Sources; Abzug, Bella S., 1920- --Photographs; Breslin, Jimmy--Photographs; Brooks, Gwendolyn 1917- --Photographs; Chavez, Cesar 1927- --Photographs; Chisholm, Shirley, 1924- --Photographs; Daly, Mary, 1928- --Photographs; Davis, Angela Yvonne, 1944- --Photographs; Davies, Diana, 1938-; Dayan, Moshe, 1915-1981--Photographs; Deming, Barbara,, 1917- --Photographs; Dworkin, Andrea--Photographs; Friedan, Betty--Photographs; Holbrook, Hal--Photographs; Jacobi, Lotte--Photographs; Jay, Karla--Photographs; Johnson, Sonia--Photographs; Joplin, Janis--Photographs; Kennedy, Edward Moore, 1932- --Photographs; Kennedy, Florynce, 1916- --Photographs; Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968--Photographs; Millett, Kate--Photographs; Price, Leontine--Photographs; Rankin, Jeanette--Photographs; Raye, Martha--Photographs; Sarton, May, 1912- --Photographs; Sontag, Susan, 1933- --Photographs; Photojourney: photographs / by Diana Davies.
Additional Information
Related Material
Smaller collections of Diana Davies' photographs are housed in the Folkways Collection at the Smithsonian Institution (photographs of musicians); Howard University; Swarthmore College Peace Collection; and at the New York Public Library. See also photographs of Students for Peaceful Resolution in the Smith College Archives.
- Biographical materials
  - Oral history: transcript and CD, 2001 (Box 1)
- Published Material, [See also Oversized materials]
  - Press passes, biog. stuff, flyers, some show info (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Exhibit: show material (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Copy of book Photojourney (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Press releases, flyers, and reviews of Photojourney (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sound recordings (music) by Diana Davies (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Copies of work done for Broadside magazine, early 1960s (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper articles on street kids art show. coastal Maine, Diana Davies curator, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Letters relating to photo work (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
  - Photos of Diana Davies by various people; drawings and photos by Kady (of D.D.), some biog. material (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Work done for Women's Rights National Historical Park, Seneca Falls, NY,photos, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Work done for Women's Rights National Historical Park and some of their info flyers (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Tear Sheets": work done for various publications and organizations - published and printed material, [Note: "Tear Sheets" are newspaper, book, magazine, journal, and poster copies and clippings of published work] (Box 2, Folder 7-12)
  - "Tear Sheets" - on the Middle East - Israel/Palestine (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Writing: play script; The War Machine. Produced for theater. Flyers, miscellaneous material, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Writings: Work zine. "Street Arts Manifesto," "Community Center," by DJD (Box 2, Folder 15)
- "Sistervision" exhibit, Sophia Smith Collection, March - June 2000
  - Photos of the exhibit (SSC has negatives), [see also binders in SSC Reading Room] (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Flyers, designs, publicity, production material, memos (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper articles, press coverage, calendar listings (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Guest book (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Photos of working on material at SSC for exhibit (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Typed caption sheets (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Duplicate copy: caption sheets for photo show (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Large caption sheets. Titles for show (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bibliography/computer print out for books by women in Sistervision - "Read" (Box 3, Folder 9)
- "Diana's Place": Matilda Joslin Gage Historical Society-- meeting place, Women's Creative Space, gallery, library, café, used goods and books shop, Northampton, MA, 1985
  - Interior views and storefront "Diana's Place" photos, flyers, info (includes Diana, Kady, Pat Styer) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Alley Cats that hung out at the space (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Laura Kaye's art show at the space and flyers for this (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Photos and info and designs and letterheads, letters. Signs from Diana's Place (includes Pat Styer and Jay Goldspinner - storyteller) (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Women's Movement - Women's Lives
  - Women's signs, banners, stickers, graffiti, and designs
    - Women's graffiti "Siembren Flores" NYC, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - "She is sad" "She is silly" sidewalk chalk graffiti, Northampton, MA, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - "The Outlaw Witches," etc., Women's graffiti, Portland, ME, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Chalk graffiti, Smith College- "Good Morning," etc., 1990s (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "She lives in a world of her own" and "Lesbians unite," etc., miscellaneous women's graffiti- slides and prints (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - "A women was raped here. Fight back." sidewalk stencil. Cambridge, MA, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Labyris, Northampton, MA (Box 5)
    - "We were the first. We will be the last" and Labrys - graffiti, Northampton, MA, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - "Women" sign - at a demo, NYC. Woman holding sign between profiles of others' faces, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - "Together we are sisters," banner, Seelye, Smith College, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Designs and drawings - Women's movement - by Diana Davies (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - "Unite It's ours" and "Sisterhood is powerful" graffiti - stencils, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - "Tip over Patriarchy" - Kady's car, bumpersticker, and cat. Northampton, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - "All Women are Beautiful" Beauty contest action, NY state (includes Kady, Barbara Deming, Yvonne Matthews Klein), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - "Christina the VW Bus," 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Women's stickers graffiti, NY state (includes Kady, Dorothy Allison, Morgan Gwenwald, others) (Box 5)
    - "Christina the V.W. Bus" - close up print of women's words, NY state, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - "Conspicuous Woman" graffiti. Portland, ME, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Angry words in public places: women's sticker art - protests - "This insults women" NY, 1970s. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - "Beware - Traditional Roles at Work" Northampton, MA, 1990s (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Transcripts of women's restroom graffiti - truck stops, diners, bars, etc. Various dates (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Women's Groups
    - Women of the sticks (group), South Jersey, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Boston-Cambridge area (Mass.) women activists (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Western mass groups-feminist activists
      - The Feminist University (includes Sonia Johnson, Elizabeth Lambert), mid 1980s - early 1990s (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - The Feminist U, The Real Reel, The Who-Ha's, (includes Kady, Pat Styer, Laura Pattison, and others), 1980s-90s (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - The Feminist U., The Who-Ha's: Kady, Marian Wagner, Pat Styer, and others., mid 1980s (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Portraits
    - Kady and women from the Women's Encampment for a Future of Peace and Justice, NY State, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Kady on steps at Pulaski Park with Pat Styer on grass at Smith College, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Kady and Pat Styer and Eileen Pagan, Western Mass, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Kady, book cover photo. Wash. Square Park, NYC, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Kady book cover photo at "Hold Hands" demo, NY and NJ- with Women's Symbol banner, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Pat Styer, Western Mass, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Pat Styer - Community and dialogue organizer, Western Mass, 1980s (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Sonia Johnson Campaign (Feminist U women), 1984
    - Feminist U. on the road and lake Champlain ferry (includes Kady, Pat Styer, Marian Wagner, Camille Norton, etc.) (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Meetings in Western Mass and Amherst College. Jacket designs and posters (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Meeting at Nancy Kelly's, N. Leverett (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Feminist U. women weaving webs and working at old Cambridge Baptist Church rally (includes Kady, Pat Styer, Euen Sperling, Laura Pattison) (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Meeting at Leah Fritz house, NYC (includes Flo Kennedy, Sonia, Grace Paley, Phyllis Chesler, Ynestra King, Karla Jay, and others) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Women's Work
    - Color slides - Miscellaneous color from "Women's Work" series - various dates (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Prints from the slides - Women's Work - (includes Yvonne Corbett Sweat Equity" Apt. builder, 1976) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Laura Pattison, Women's Café founder, activist, librarian (Box 6)
    - Tractor driver and info, Cuba, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Jackie Ball, teacher in "El Barrio," NYC, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - "Friends at Market" and the basket shop. Public market in Libson, Portugal, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Women at flea market, NYC, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - UFW - Strawberry pickers and supporters and 5-college groups demo, Hadley, Mass. (includes Daisy Rooks, Gretchen Purser - Union organizers, UFW and SLAC) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Freema the Boathaulter and Lisa Garrison and May William's Boatyard, 1977. Maine - "Women at Sea" (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Ellen Barrett - One of the first U.S. women Episcopal priests, at a Women's Rights demo, NYC, circa 1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - "Healer of Broken Dolls" - "Esperanza" and her shop. Havana, Cuba, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Kady - crafts woman with her work - wooden and metal double-axes, Forestburgh, NY, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - "The Fish Cabin" old shack Kady worked on/fixed-up, NY state, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Building/working-on Kady's "Pole-Barn" house, NY state (includes Kady, others)-- "Women Build," 1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - "Emma's Snack Bar," Western Mass, "Dot's God Deals," Maine, 1990s. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - "Adrienne's Hot Dogs" - Woman's Lunch Wagon, Coastal Maine, 1990s. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - "Beetle's Lunch" Alliston, Mass (includes Laura Pattison, Sheila Pepe and video-theatre women Michelle Baxter and Michelle Gisser), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - "Beetle's Lunch" (includes Laura Pattison, Ellen Sperling), Alliston, Mass, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Mary Hynes, craftswoman, Western Mass, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Carol Clement, Filmmaker and artist, NY State, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Bea Kreloff, artist, NY, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Women and Dance (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Cathi Finney, puppetmaker, puppet and theatre woman, Maine, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Sherry Mestel, clown, social worker, activist, writer, publisher, NJ, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Elizabeth Nutting, artist, street theatre woman, sea-faring woman, Western Mass, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Theatre and dance woman, Imogene, 1969, NYC (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Theatre - video women Michelle Baxter and Michelle Gabow, Alliston, MA, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Zoë Lewis, musician, 1992 at Hampshire College, Amherst, MA (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Willie Mae "Big Mama" Thornton, blues singer, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - "Bougainvillea" - a women's jazz band, UMass, Amherst (includes Jeannette Muzima), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Jana Byrdd-Howes, jazz musician/saxophonist, Western Mass, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Musicians Amy Greene and Aimee Swift, Western Mass, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - "Flower Thief" Women's rock band, Western Mass (includes Christine Geisler-Andrews, Catherine McRae, Jen Gallahorn), 1995 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Writings (miscellaneous) on women's work (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Women's Play
    - Girl playing in window - dancing and laughing - NYCand street murals, Lower East side, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Little girl at a street festival - Street theatre event (with bicycles), Maine, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Little girl with streamers at street festival, Maine, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Girls and grandmother, Chinatown (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Hopscotch design - chalk on sidewalk, Western Mass "Queen of the Hopscotch," 1992 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - "Skate sisters" - sister skaters, W. 72nd St., NYC, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - "The Skateboard Sisters," Pulaski Park, Northampton, MA, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - The Lesbian and Women's Café. Gay Activists Alliance (GAA) Firehouse, NYC, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - "Amanda Hits the Road"--little girl at street fair, Western Mass, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - "Soul Sister #1" --Women singing together at Street rally - African American songs, Washington D.C., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - The little girl with the cat, NYC streets, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous: women travelers cooking out, little girl drawing on sidewalk, women "piggy-back" riding, etc. (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Women's Friendship
    - Bessie Jones and Leola Polite Harris, at L.P.H's farm, Georgia Sea Islands and farm animals, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - "Three Life Long Friends," NYC, Parish Hall(3 older women), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Friends on a porch, Memphis, TN (2 older women and 2 little girls), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Writers Sybil Clairbourne and Grace Paley, with bicycles, NYC, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Kady with Alice Miller and Margaret Lorick - older women's music festival, friends, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - 3 older women at Shelburne Falls senior center tag sale event, Western Mass, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Women's Best Friends (animal friends)
    - Kady and Billy the cat, W. Burke, VT, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Kady and her dog friend "George" and Billie Jean cat, NY State, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Kady and dog friend "George," NY State, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Best friend "Gertrude" (dog), NYC, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Cat friend "Max" in window, NYC, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Woman and dog at picnic in Central Park, NYC, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Women's Worlds (scenes from our lives)
    - Miscellaneous color slides and prints from slides (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - "Women's Worlds" - miscellaneous b&w scenes (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Woman on subway, NYC, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Sports
    - Volleyball game, NYC, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Softball game, Hurleyville, NY, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - CR Groups (consciousness-raising), NY state (includes Kady, Barbara Deming, others), 1970s (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Sagaris: The Feminist Institute (includes Diane Adler, Ti-Grace Atkinson, Bonnie Bluh, Blanche McCary Boyd, Margaret Fiedler, March Hoffman {Artemis March}, Martha Kearns, Kathryn Kilgore, Cheryl Muzio, Grace Paley, Joan Peters, Roberta Schine, Susan Sherman, Alix Kates Shulman, Shoshana, Margaret Sloan, and Barbara Seaman), Lyndonville, VT, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 64-65)
    - Feminist Writer's meeting and reading at Sagaris (includes Kady, Yvonne Matthews Klein, Margaret Fielder, Jessie Taras), 1975 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Women and Social Justice
    - Miscellaneous: b&w (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Sarah Hodak, Youth Rights worker and community organizer and hobo Northampton, MA, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Fannie Lou Hamer, civil rights organizer, circa 1965 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Angela Yvonne Davis, writer, historian, social justice activist, professor, NYC, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Marian Wagner, feminist activist, social justice worker, teacher, VT, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Vilette Brewer's house, with "Better Housing," etc. sign--poor people's campaign. Tent city, Washington D.C., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Dorothy Day-Catholic worker and peace movement work, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Demo at NYU for students' rights and gay rights and social justice, NYC "All Power to the People," 1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - "Justice for Janitors" at Women and Civil Rights conference, Atlanta, GA (includes Myles Horton, Rosa Parks), 1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Toward Dawn by DJD: writing about Dawn Levy, So. African human rights activist, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - "Agents for Social Change": conference material and photos, Sophia Smith Collection, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Women and Peace
    - Kady and her "Eliminate the Military" sewn banner, Western Mass, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Susan Sontag reading at "Angry Arts Against the War in Vietnam," NYC (includes Paul Blackburn, poet) a week long/all day-night event, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Nuns at an anti-war rally, NYC, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - "Nighttime Peace March and Dump Nixon Demo" NYC; "Vietnam Death Toll Sign" held by old woman, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (WILPF) members with sign. Peace march, NYC and right wing hecklers, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Women participants and musicians "The Penny Whistlers" at a peace march, NYC (includes Ethel Raim, musicologist), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Jailed and arrested war tax resisters - Kady in the Pokey. Marian Wagner and Juanita Nelson arrested, Colrain and Greenfield, MA, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Action to stop selective service registration, Northampton HS, Western Mass (includes Kady, AFSC, RAY, and other groups), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Stop the war against Iraq demo, Federal building, Springfield, Mass (includes Kady with "No War" sign), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Women activists in "the Tombs" jail, at "Stop the Draft Week," NYC, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Girls with "Vietnam Moratoruim" sign, NYC, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous color slides of "Women and Peace" (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Jeannette Rankin Brigade anti-Vietnam war demo and march, Washington D.C.(includes Jeannette Rakin, Ella Baker, Judy Collins, Barbara Deming, Coretta Scott King, Denise Levertov, Viveca Lindfors, Toshi Alline Seeger), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous peace movement (b&w ) (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Women march for world disarmament, Northampton, Mass (includes Frances Crowe, Kathryn Kirk, Laura Kaye, Mary Hynes), late 1980s (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Woman with sign "Just Send our Sons Home" anti-war demo, Union Square, NYC, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Women against Nukes, various events Western Mass (includes Kady) Street theatre, etc., 1990s (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Women's movement miscellaneous